Guide to the Laura McPhee River of No Return Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographic Material, 2003–2008; Series I
  - Oversize Prints, 2006–2008
    - Chromogenic Color Prints, 28 x 35.5 cm, 2008
      - Book Proofs Set, 2008
        - Mattie with a Plymouth Barred Rock Hen, Laverty Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 5, Negative Number 6471), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 134)
        - Sagebrush and Grass in an Irrigated Field, Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 6, Negative Number 2145), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 135)
        - Sorting Black Angus Cow/Calf Pairs, Morgan Williams Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2003 (Page 7, Negative Number 8043), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 136)
        - Mattie with a Bourbon Red Turkey, Laverty Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 9, Negative Number 2970), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 137)
        - Gamaniel Tacza, Peruvian Sheperd, Fourth of July Creek, White Cloud Mountains, Idaho, 2003 (Page 10, Negative Number 6048), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 138)
        - Aspens Carved by Sheep Herders, Fisher Creek, White Cloud Mountains, Idaho, Summer Solstice, 2003 (Page 11, Negative Number 6548), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 139)
        - Rocks from Sawtooth National Forest for Landscaping in Sun Valley, Pettit Lake Road, Blaine County, Idaho, 2003 (Page 13, Negative Number 6575), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 140)
        - Nineteen-twenties Settler's Cabin at the Edge of a Subdivision, Sawtooth Valley, Idaho, 2003 (Page 14, Negative Number 6254), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 141)
        - Three Rivers Stone Quarry, Clayton, Idaho, 2008 (Page 15, Negative Number 94086) (Box 8, Folder 142)
        - Little Redfish Lake Campground, Custer County, Idaho, 2003 (Page 16, Negative Number 7821), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 143)
        - Tom Thurber Cutting Firewood, Lost Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2003 (Page 17, Negative Number 7761), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 144)
        - Mark Anderson Panning for Gold in 19th Century Tailings, Joe's Gulch, Lower Stanley, Idaho, 2003 (Page 18, Negative Number 8033), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 145)
        - Cyanide Evaporation Pool by the River of No Return Wilderness, Grouse Creek Lead, Silver and Gold Mine, Yankee Fork, Idaho, 2005 (Page 19, Negative Number 2073), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 146)
        - Salvage, Custer County Transfer Station, Stanley, Idaho, 2004 (Page 21, Negative Number 6345), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 147)
        - Ladies' Changing Room, Clayton Lead-Silver Mine, Kinnikinik Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 24, Negative Number 2920), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 148)
        - Nineteen-forties Women's Magazines at the Manager's House at the Bayhorse Lead-Silver Mine, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 25, Negative Number 2111), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 149)
        - Nineteen-Seventies Magazine, Old Obsidian, Idaho, 2004 (Page 26, Negative Number 6349), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 150)
        - Master Bedroom, Manager's House, Clayton Lead-Silver Mine, Kinnikinik Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 27, Negative Number 2964), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 151)
        - Depression Glass (Made with Uranium) and Fluorite Under a Black Light, Sawtooth City, Idaho, 2005 (Page 29, Negative Number 641), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 152)
        - Isobel, Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 31, Negative Number 6356), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 153)
        - Irrigation Ditch, Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 33, Negative Number 6379), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 154)
        - Floating Dock Beached for Winter, Alturas Lake, Blaine County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 34, Negative Number 2993), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 155)
        - Matt Visiting Shepherd's Camp Near Lost Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2003 (Page 35, Negative Number 5965), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 156)
        - Mattie, Bob, and Bo, Road Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 37, Negative Number 2095), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 157)
        - Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, May 31, 2005 (Page 39, Negative Number 2135), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 158)
        - Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, June 21, 2003 (Page 40, Negative Number 6542), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 159)
        - Red Fladry to Spook Wolves and Deter Them from Killing Claves, Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, September 30, 2003 (Page 41, Negative Number 7864), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 160)
        - Fourth of July Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, July 8, 2004 (Page 42, Negative Number 6584), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 161)
        - Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, July 15, 2004 (Page 43, Negative Number 6380), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 162)
        - Moon Setting, Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, January 27, 2008 (Page 45, Negative Number 94090) (Box 9, Folder 163)
        - Quatered Rocky Mountain Elk, Milky Creek, White Cloud Mountains, Idaho, 2004 (Page 47, Negative Number 2929), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 164)
        - Skinned Elk, White Cloud Mountains, Idaho, 2004 (Page 48, Negative Number 2943), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 165)
        - Elk Heart and Liver, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 49, Negative Number 2932), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 166)
        - Chest Cavity, Rocky Mountain Cow Elk, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 51, Negative Number 2941), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 167)
        - Antlers in the Rafters of a Barn, Highway 75 near Gold Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 53, Negative Number 8016), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 168)
        - Isaac Babcock, Biologist for the Nez Pierce Tribe, Dressed for Tranquilizing and Radio-Collaring Wolves, Fourth of July Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2003 (Page 55, Negative Number 8028), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 169)
        - Judy Tracking Radio-Collared Wolves From Her Yard, Summer Range, H-Hook Ranch Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 57, Negative Number 6585), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 170)
        - Mattie in Her Eighth Grade Graduation Dress Holding a Robin's Nest, Laverty Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, May 2005 (Page 59, Negative Number 2148), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 171)
        - Endangered Sockeye Salmon Fry, Main Vat Room, Sawtooth Fish Hatchery, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 60, Negative Number 9753), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 172)
        - Alturas Lake Outlet, Blaine County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 61, Negative Number 2922), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 173)
        - Winter Sampling to Study Growth and Diet of Endangered Snake River Sockeye Salmon, Pettit Lake, Blaine County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 63, Negative Number 9562), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 174)
        - Air Bladder of an Endangered Sockeye Salmon, Pettit Lake, Blaine County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 64, Negative Number 686), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 175)
        - Rob Trahant, Shoshone-Bannock Tribal Member, Counting Fish for Juvenile Chinook Salmon Survey, Valley Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 65, Negative Number 6484), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 176)
        - Breached Dam at Sunbeam on the Salmon River, Custer County, Idaho, 2003 (Page 67, Negative Number 8060), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 177)
        - Angler's Path Among Willows, Valley Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 68, Negative Number 6492), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 178)
        - Fly Line for Steelhead, Robinson Bar, Salmon River, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 69, Negative Number 689), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 179)
        - Cascade, Redfish Lake Creek, Sawtooth Wilderness, Idaho, 2004 (Page 73, Negative Number 6494), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 180)
        - Tire Swing, Alturas Lake, Blaine County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 74, Negative Number 710), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 181)
        - Bob Cutting Ice, Stanley Lake, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 75, Negative Number 650), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 182)
        - Campfire, H-Hook Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 77, Negative Number 9745), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 183)
        - Snowmobile Headlights, Valley Road, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 78, Negative Number 9609), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 184)
        - Leghold Traps and Pelts of Raccoon and Foxes, Sawtooth Fish Hatchery, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 79, Negative Number 687), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 185)
        - Igloo Built From Downloaded Plans, Park Creek Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 81, Negative Number 643), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 186)
        - Nineteen-forties Women's Magazines at the Manager's House at the Bayhorse Lead-Silver Mine, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 82, Negative Number 2112), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 187)
        - Judy with Elk Heart, H-Hook Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 83, Negative Number 2912), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 188)
        - Fox Confiscated from a Leghold Trap at Rough Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 84, Negative Number 673), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 189)
        - Illegally Kept Snake River Chinook Salmon with Freezer Burn, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 85, Negative Number 658), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 190)
        - Lodgepole Pines Killed by Beetles, Nip and Tuck Road, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 89, Negative Number 2106), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 191)
        - Smoke from a Wildfire Ignited by Sparks from a Burn Barrel, Champion Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 91, Negative Number 3687), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 192)
        - Smoke Above Fisher Creek, Valley Road Wildfire, 40,838 Acres Burned, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 92, Negative Number 3703), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 193)
        - Burned Timber, Fourth of July Creek, Valley Road Wildfire, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 93, Negative Number 3676), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 194)
        - Understory Flareups, Fourth of July Creek, Valley Road Wildfire, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 95, Negative Number 3698), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 195)
        - Mattie, Fisher Creek Turnout, Challis School District, Idaho, 2004 (Page 97, Negative Number 9573), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 196)
        - Sawtooth Range, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 99, Negative Number 9641), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 197)
        - Washington Peak, White Cloud Mountains, Custer County, Idaho, 2008 (Page 123, Negative Number 94082) (Box 10, Folder 198)
        - Regrowth, Closed Road Near Aztec Mine, Custer County, Idaho, 2007 (Page 125, Negative Number 92854), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 199)
        - In Fourth of July Creek Canyon Looking West, Custer County, Idaho, 2007 (Page 127, Negative not extant), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 200)
      - Book Proofs Set, 2008
        Folders with two prints include images published on pages 11, 41, 84, and 99 of the book. Lack prints for images published on pages 13, 15, 16, 17, 21, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 29, 34, 47, 53, 67, 79, 82, 87, 97, 123, 125, and 127.
        - Irrigator's Tarp Directing Water, Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Pages ii and 102, Negative Number 6341), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 201)
        - One Car Passing, Valley Road, Sawtooth Valley, Idaho, 2003 (Page 3, Negative Number 6584-1520), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 202)
        - Mattie with a Plymouth Barred Rock Hen, Laverty Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 5, Negative Number 6471), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 203)
        - Sagebrush and Grass in an Irrigated Field, Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 6, Negative Number 2145), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 204)
        - Sorting Black Angus Cow/Calf Pairs, Morgan Williams Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2003 (Page 7, Negative Number 8043), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 205)
        - Mattie with a Bourbon Red Turkey, Laverty Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 9, Negative Number 2970), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 206)
        - Gamaniel Tacza, Peruvian Sheperd, Fourth of July Creek, White Cloud Mountains, Idaho, 2003 (Page 10, Negative Number 6048), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 207)
        - Aspens Carved by Sheep Herders, Fisher Creek, White Cloud Mountains, Idaho, Summer Solstice, 2003 (Page 11, Negative Number 6548), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 208)
          2 photographic prints.
        - Nineteen-twenties Settler's Cabin at the Edge of a Subdivision, Sawtooth Valley, Idaho, 2003 (Page 14, Negative Number 6254), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 209)
        - Mark Anderson Panning for Gold in 19th Century Tailings, Joe's Gulch, Lower Stanley, Idaho, 2003 (Page 18, Negative Number 8033), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 210)
        - Cyanide Evaporation Pool by the River of No Return Wilderness, Grouse Creek Lead, Silver and Gold Mine, Yankee Fork, Idaho, 2005 (Page 19, Negative Number 2073), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 211)
        - Isobel, Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 31, Negative Number 6356), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 212)
        - Irrigation Ditch, Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 33, Negative Number 6379), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 213)
        - Matt Visiting Shepherd's Camp Near Lost Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2003 (Page 35, Negative Number 5965), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 214)
        - Mattie, Bob, and Bo, Road Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 37, Negative Number 2095), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 215)
        - Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, May 31, 2005 (Page 39, Negative Number 2135), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 216)
        - Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, June 21, 2003 (Page 40, Negative Number 6542), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 217)
        - Red Fladry to Spook Wolves and Deter Them from Killing Claves, Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, September 30, 2003 (Page 41, Negative Number 7864), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 218)
        - Fourth of July Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, July 8, 2004 (Page 42, Negative Number 6584), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 219)
        - Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, July 15, 2004 (Page 43, Negative Number 6380), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 220)
        - Moon Setting, Fourth of July Creek Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, January 27, 2008 (Page 45, Negative Number 94090) (Box 11, Folder 221)
        - Skinned Elk, White Cloud Mountains, Idaho, 2004 (Page 48, Negative Number 2943), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 222)
        - Elk Heart and Liver, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 49, Negative Number 2932), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 223)
        - Chest Cavity, Rocky Mountain Cow Elk, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 51, Negative Number 2941), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 224)
        - Isaac Babcock, Biologist for the Nez Pierce Tribe, Dressed for Tranquilizing and Radio-Collaring Wolves, Fourth of July Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2003 (Page 55, Negative Number 8028), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 225)
        - Judy Tracking Radio-Collared Wolves From Her Yard, Summer Range, H-Hook Ranch Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 57, Negative Number 6585), 2008 (Box 11, Folder 226)
        - Mattie in Her Eighth Grade Graduation Dress Holding a Robin's Nest, Laverty Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, May 2005 (Page 59, Negative Number 2148), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 227)
        - Endangered Sockeye Salmon Fry, Main Vat Room, Sawtooth Fish Hatchery, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 60, Negative Number 9753), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 228)
        - Alturas Lake Outlet, Blaine County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 61, Negative Number 2922), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 229)
        - Winter Sampling to Study Growth and Diet of Endangered Snake River Sockeye Salmon, Pettit Lake, Blaine County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 63, Negative Number 9562), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 230)
        - Air Bladder of an Endangered Sockeye Salmon, Pettit Lake, Blaine County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 64, Negative Number 686), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 231)
        - Rob Trahant, Shoshone-Bannock Tribal Member, Counting Fish for Juvenile Chinook Salmon Survey, Valley Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 65, Negative Number 6484), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 232)
        - Angler's Path Among Willows, Valley Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 68, Negative Number 6492), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 233)
        - Fly Line for Steelhead, Robinson Bar, Salmon River, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 69, Negative Number 689), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 234)
        - Mattie in Her Grandmother's Wedding Dress, Laverty Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, May 2005 (Page 71, Negative Number 2097), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 235)
        - Cascade, Redfish Lake Creek, Sawtooth Wilderness, Idaho, 2004 (Page 73, Negative Number 6494), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 236)
        - Tire Swing, Alturas Lake, Blaine County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 74, Negative Number 710), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 237)
        - Bob Cutting Ice, Stanley Lake, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 75, Negative Number 650), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 238)
        - Campfire, H-Hook Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 77, Negative Number 9745), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 239)
        - Snowmobile Headlights, Valley Road, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 78, Negative Number 9609), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 240)
        - Igloo Built From Downloaded Plans, Park Creek Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 81, Negative Number 643), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 241)
        - Judy with Elk Heart, H-Hook Ranch, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 83, Negative Number 2912), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 242)
        - Fox Confiscated from a Leghold Trap at Rough Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 84, Negative Number 673), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 243)
        - Illegally Kept Snake River Chinook Salmon with Freezer Burn, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 85, Negative Number 658), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 244)
        - Lodgepole Pines Killed by Beetles, Nip and Tuck Road, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 89, Negative Number 2106), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 245)
        - Smoke from a Wildfire Ignited by Sparks from a Burn Barrel, Champion Creek, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 91, Negative Number 3687), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 246)
        - Smoke Above Fisher Creek, Valley Road Wildfire, 40,838 Acres Burned, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 92, Negative Number 3703), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 247)
        - Burned Timber, Fourth of July Creek, Valley Road Wildfire, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 93, Negative Number 3676), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 248)
        - Understory Flareups, Fourth of July Creek, Valley Road Wildfire, Custer County, Idaho, 2005 (Page 95, Negative Number 3698), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 249)
        - Sawtooth Range, Custer County, Idaho, 2004 (Page 99, Negative Number 9641), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 250)
      - Proofs Not Used in Book, 2008
        Arranged chronologically under headings for the year of image capture and then sequentially by negative number.
        - Images Captured in 2003, 2008
          - Untitled, 2003 (Negative Number 6000), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 251)
          - Untitled, 2003 (Negative Number 6116), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 252)
          - Untitled, 2003 (Negative Number 6118), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 253)
          - Untitled, 2003 (Negative Number 6119), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 254)
          - Untitled, 2003 (Negative Number 6547), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 255)
          - Untitled, 2003 (Negative Number 6580), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 256)
          - Untitled, 2003 (Negative Number 6583), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 257)
          - Untitled, 2003 (Negative Number 7855), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 258)
          - Untitled, 2003 (Negative Number 7894), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 259)
          - Untitled, 2003 (Negative Number 8036), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 260)
          - Untitled, 2003 (Negative Number 8059), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 261)
        - Images Captured in 2004, 2008
          - Untitled, 2004 (Negative Number 2919), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 262)
          - Untitled, 2004 (Negative Number 2956), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 263)
          - Untitled, 2004 (Negative Number 3017), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 264)
          - Untitled, 2004 (Negative Number 4005), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 265)
          - Untitled, 2004 (Negative Number 6340), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 266)
          - Untitled, 2004 (Negative Number 6353), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 267-268)
          - Untitled, 2004 (Negative Number 6383), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 269)
          - Untitled, 2004 (Negative Number 6472), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 270)
          - Untitled, 2004 (Negative Number 6493), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 271)
          - Untitled, 2004 (Negative Number 6503), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 272)
          - Untitled, 2004 (Negative Number 6586), 2008 (Box 13, Folder 273)
          - Untitled, 2004 (Negative Number 9555), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 274)
          - Untitled, 2004 (Negative Number 9787), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 275)
          - Untitled, 2004 (Negative Number 9793), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 276)
        - Images Captured in 2005, 2008
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 632), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 277)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 638), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 278)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 644), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 279)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 664), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 280)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 665), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 281)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 666), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 282)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 668), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 283)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 690), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 284)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 695), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 285)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 717), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 286)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 2074), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 287)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 2079), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 288)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 2081), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 289)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 2088), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 290)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 2117), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 291)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 2122), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 292)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 2124), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 293)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 2124, varient), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 294)
            Verso of print identified as printed from Negative Number 2124, but it depicts a varient image made from a non-extant negative.
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 2129), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 295)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 2130), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 296)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 2139), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 297)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 2146), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 298)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 2519), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 299)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 2524), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 300)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 3678), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 301)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 3696), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 302)
          - Untitled, 2005 (Negative Number 3708), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 303)
        - Images without an Image Capture Date, 2008
          - Untitled (Negative Number 6937), 2008 (Box 14, Folder 304)
            Verso of print identified as printed from Negative Number 6937, a non-extant negative.
  - Work Prints, 2003–2008
    Work prints for all negatives created by Laura McPhee during her residency in the Sawtooth Valley, Idaho, 2003-2008.
    Each folder houses a single print except where noted.
    Arranged under two headings: Chromogenic Color Prints and Black-and-white Prints.
    - Chromogenic Color Prints, 2003–2008
      Chromogenic color prints on Kodak Professional Endura paper, 20.2 x 25.1 cm.
      - Images Captured in 2003
        - Negative Numbers 5962 to 5971, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 305-314)
        - Negative Number 6000, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 315)
        - Negative Number 6000, Varient 1, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 316)
        - Negative Number 6022, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 317)
        - Negative Number 6022, Varient 1, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 318)
        - Negative Numbers 6023, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 319)
        - Negative Numbers 6025 to 6029, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 320-324)
        - Negative Number 6033, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 325)
        - Negative Numbers 6047 to 6051, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 326-330)
        - Negative Number 6110, printed 2003 June (Box 15, Folder 331)